realtytrac.com 2012-12-13

# RealtyTrac - Privacy Policy

**PLEASE NOTE:** OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME. PLEASE CHECK BACK FOR UPDATES.

Use of this website is not intended by persons under 18 years of age. You acknowledge that by using this web site and/or providing information and registering to use this site and through the submission of information requested, you agree and approve of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and subsequent amendments to this Privacy Policy by your continued use of this website. This Privacy Policy shall govern our use and disclosure of your personal information. If you do not agree and approve of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, you are advised and instructed not to continue and not to complete the registration process (i.e. do not register) or otherwise use or access this site. [Please Opt Out by clicking on this link to be forwarded to our opt-out process](http://www.realtytrac.com/pub/optout.asp).

This Privacy Policy will provide details and describe how and what information about you is gathered, used, and distributed as a function of this website.

We appreciate that the information you provide to us and that we gather may be personal and private. Some of this information is used to facilitate improvements to our website and to enhance your RealtyTrac experience. We will/may share information about you with our business affiliates who have provided or may provide goods or services in connection with this site.

RealtyTrac compiles personal information about you when you register to use this site; when you use or purchase products and services through this site; when you connect or transfer to or from affiliate sites; when you participate in promotions; and when you ask to be provided additional services. The documentation that we gather enables us to analyze a User's and/or Member's interests and preferences, develop new services and enhance current services, improve your experience, and create meaningful affiliate relationships. The type of personal information that RealtyTrac may gather includes first name; last name; e-mail address; address; city, state and zip code; telephone number; facsimile number; credit card type; credit card number; expiration date of credit card; name on credit card; first name as it appears on check; last name as it appears on check; bank routing number as it appears on check; checking account number; driver's license number; state in which driver's license was issued; date of birth; company name; business telephone number; MLS ID number (if a licensed real estate agent); preferred listings; last five (5) searches; custom saved searches; customer communications, correspondence, e-mails, faxes and customer service/member service memos; customer responses to questionnaires and surveys; the Web address where members enter from and exit to; and which pages you visit during your use of this site. 

RealtyTrac may place and access cookies on your computer. RealtyTrac affiliates that offer goods and/or services on or through this site may place and access cookies on your computer. Cookies placed by affiliates are controlled by the affiliate's own privacy policy.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to other companies, entities or individuals without your consent or approval. We do share your personal information in the following events:

  * if we are provided your consent or approval;
  * to establish and maintain your membership;
  * to process payment for goods, services and membership provided to you;
  * to assist you in obtaining the goods and services you request;
  * to assist in making offers, promotions, goods and/or services from RealtyTrac and/or third party(ies) that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * to update, improve, modify or enhance the operations of this website;
  * in response to a subpoena, court order or other legal process;
  * to assist law enforcement or other appropriate entities which we believe in good faith are conducting examinations or investigations of possible fraud or illegal activities;
  * to investigate possible violations of our Terms of Use Agreement; or
  * pursuant to a transfer of ownership of RealtyTrac Inc.

Your personal information is encrypted and appropriate measures are taken to protect against unauthorized or inappropriate use of your personal information.

RealtyTrac Community Content. The RealtyTrac Community portion of the RealtyTrac.com website contains sections (aka forums or message boards) where readers and users can submit and publish comments, questions, and answers. We do not actively monitor these sections, and RealtyTrac, its affiliates, and content licensors assume no liability for any content therein, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use login validation for most of our Community in order to reduce "comment spam." While your email address will not be published, the actual content of the any comments, questions, and answers you submit are considered public property. Do not offer any personal information in any content you submit, unless you want that information displayed publically to the online world. We will remove "comment spam" from our Community sections at our discretion.

You may contact our customer service department to update or correct your personal information at anytime. If you wish to opt out of receiving further communication from us regarding future promotions or other goods and services, please contact our customer service department. Please know that depending on what opt-out choices you select, your ability to maintain your membership and continue to obtain goods and services may be affected. Our customer service department can be reached by e-mail at [support@realtytrac.com](mailto:support@realtytrac.com); by telephone at 877.888.8722; and by facsimile transmission at 949.305.0803. The effective date of any opt-out action will be ten (10) business days following the date your opt-out request is received by RealtyTrac, after which your e-mail address will be added to the suppression files associated with this site.

If you want to request to be removed from further communication with this site, including our Premium Services, please opt out by clicking on this link to our opt-out procedure. We will place your e-mail address on a suppression file associated with this site. Persons whose names appear on our suppression file will have their e-mail addresses checked against all correspondence to be sent by us. Where there is a match, the planned e-mail correspondence will be withheld, and such persons will receive no further e-mail correspondence from us. Your e-mail address will be placed on the suppression list associated with this site following ten (10) business days of the day your opt-out request is received by RealtyTrac.

We may unilaterally amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new privacy policy on the site. Be sure to check the current terms of any privacy policy in effect by visiting this site. By checking the effective date of the policy, you will know whether the Privacy Policy has been amended. Please note however, that all amended terms, or the new privacy policy shall automatically become effective thirty (30) days after initial posting.

If you choose not to accept or do not agree to be bound by the terms of the revised or amended Privacy Policy, then you must opt out and terminate your RealtyTrac Membership before the effective date of the revised or amended Privacy Policy. Your failure to take advantage of the opt-out provisions prior to the effective date of the revised or amended Privacy Policy will constitute your agreement and approval to be bound by the revised or amended Privacy Policy after its effective date.

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. Please note that if our information practices change at some time in the future, we will use only data collected from the time of the new policy amendment forward for those new purposes.

**Special Notification for California Residents**

Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following mailing address: CA Privacy Request, One Venture Plaza, Suite 300, Irvine, California, 92618. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph.

This Privacy Policy is effective beginning September 21, 2008.
